{
    "subject": "resource/Nasum",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Burning_Heart_Records_artists",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Nasum is Burning Heart Records artists.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8729234337806702,
            "question": "How has Nasum contributed to the Burning Heart Records label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8356812000274658,
            "question": "How might Nasum's music be categorized based on their association with Burning Heart Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7785958647727966,
            "question": "Who are some Burning Heart Records artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464627623558044,
            "question": "Are there other bands similar to Nasum that are also signed to Burning Heart Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766672730445862,
            "question": "Is Nasum associated with a record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5819222331047058,
            "question": "What are some notable releases by artists signed to Burning Heart Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266956090927124,
            "question": "What kind of music is likely produced by Burning Heart Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.476003497838974,
            "question": "Does Burning Heart Records focus on a specific genre of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4438894987106323,
            "question": "What is the history of Burning Heart Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40960264205932617,
            "question": "Can you name any famous musicians signed to Burning Heart Records?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Nasum is Burning Heart Records artists.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7138_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Burning Heart Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7138_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Burning Heart Records focus on a specific genre of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7138_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music is likely produced by Burning Heart Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7138_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7138_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe text documents describe Nasum as a Swedish grindcore band that was formed in 1992, released four studio albums, and disbanded after the December 2004 tsunami killed their frontman Mieszko Talarczyk. They also mention that Nasum reunited with Rotten Sound frontman Keijo Niinimaa in 2012 for a one-off tour to celebrate their 20th anniversary.\n\nThere is no information provided that suggests Nasum was an artist affiliated with Burning Heart Records, or any other record label besides Poserslaughter Records."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Nasum, a band that has been associated with the record label Relapse and later with Burning Heart records. The statements in the query align with the context provided, confirming that Nasum is indeed related to artists of Burning Heart Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Nasum recently made the jump to Sweden\u2019s own Burning Heart records, indicating they are now associated with that label, not solely Relapse Records.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}